Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- New York State Committee - Pasmore, William, Jeffrey Haldeman., Publication (Box 19)
  - Pasmore, William, Gary Frank and Bob Rehm, "Developing Citizenship for the Active Organization", Publication (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - Item 1: Developing Citizenship for the Active Organization, 1991; Publication (Box 19, Folder 134)
      Author: William Pasmore, Gary Frank, and Bob Rehm
  - Pasmore, William A., "Overcoming the Roadblocks in Work-Restructuring Efforts", Publication (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - Item 1: Overcoming the Roadblocks in Work-Restructuring Efforts, 1982; Publication (Box 19, Folder 135)
      Author: William A. Pasmore
  - Pasmore, William, Jeff Peter and Richard Bastian, "Sociotechnical Systems in Health Care: A Field Experiment that Failed", Publication (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - Item 1: Sociotechnical Systems in Health Care: A Field Experiment that Failed, 1985; Publication (Box 19, Folder 136)
      Author: William Pasmore, Jeff Peter, and Richard Bastian
  - Pasmore, William, Jeffrey Haldeman, Carole Francis and Abraham B. Shani, "Sociotechnical Systems: A Review and Appraisal", Publication (Box 19, Folder 137)
    - Item 1: Socio-technical Systems: A Review and Appraisal, 1979; Publication (Box 19, Folder 137)
      Author: William Pasmore, Jeffrey Haldeman, Carole Francis, and Abraham B. Shani
- Patchin, Robert I - Radius., Publication (Box 20)
  - Patchin, Robert I., "Quality Control Circles in an Office Environment", Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Quality Control Circles in an Office Envrionment, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Author: Robert I. Patchin
  - Patchin, Robert I., "Remarks on Quality Control Circles: Northup's Experience", Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Remarks on Quality Circles: Northrup's Experience, 1984; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Patchin, Robert I., "Where are We Headed With Quality Control Circles?", Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Where Are We Headed with Circles?, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Author: Robert Patchin
  - Patterson, William Pat, "Where is Technology Taking Us?", Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Where Is Technology Taking Us?, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Author: William Pat Patterson
  - Patton, Spiro G., "Tourism and Local Economic Development: Factory Outlets and the Reading SMSA", Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Tourism and Local Economic Development: Factory Outlets and the Reading SMSA, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Author: Spiro G. Patton
  - Pauly, David, "2001: A Union Odyssey", Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: 2001: A Union Odyssey, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Author: David Pauly
  - Paulin, George B. "Long-Term Incentives for Management: An Overview", Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Long-Term Incentives for Management: An Overview, 1989; Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Author: George B. Paulin
  - "Pay for Knowledge: Is it Practical?", Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Pay for Knowledge: Is It Practical?, 1987; Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Pearce, James, "The Minimum Wage and the Davis-Bacon Act: Comment", Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: The Minimum Wage and the Davis-Bacon Act: Comment, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Author: James Pearce
  - Pearson, Andrall E. "Corporate Redemption and the Seven Deadly Sins", Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Corporate Redemption and the Seven Deadly Sins, 1992; Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Author: Andrall E. Pearson
  - Peck, Charles A., Top Executive Compensation: 1987 Edition, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Top Executive Compensation: 1987 Edition, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Author: Charles A. Peck
  - Peck, Cornelius J., "A Proposal to End NLRB Deferral to the Arbitration Process", Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: A Proposal to End NLRB Deferral to the Arbitration Process, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Author: Cornelius J. Peck
  - Pennar, Karen, "Its Time to Put Our Money Where Our Mouth is", Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Its Time to Put Our Money Where Our Mouth Is, 1988; Publication (Box 20, Folder 13)
      Author: Karen Pennar
  - Peon-Escalante, J.I. The Total Equality Movement in Mexico May, 1991, Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: The Total Quality Movement in Mexico, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Author: J.I. Peon-Escalante
  - Percorini, Steven, "Alternative Work Structures: An Analysis of Change and Resistance", Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Alternative Work Structures: An Analysis of Change and Resistance, 1980; Publication (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Author: Steven Percorini
  - "Performance Management Project Report", Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Performance Management Project Report, 1984; Publication (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Perham, John, "Flexible Benefits are Spreading Fast", Publication (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Flexible Benefits are Spreading Fast, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Author: John Perham
  - Perlman, Mark. "Labor Movement Theories: Past, Present, and Future", Publication (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Labor Movement Theories: Past, Present, and Future, 1960; Publication (Box 20, Folder 18)
      Author: Mark Perlman
  - Perot, H. Ross, "Love, War and Sports as a Language of Leadership", Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Love, War, and Sports As Language of Leadership, 1987; Publication (Box 20, Folder 19)
      Author: H. Ross Perot
  - Perrakis, Stylianos, "The Labor-Surplus Model and Wage Behavior in Mexico", Publication (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: The Labor-Surplus Model and Wage Behavior in Mexico, 1972; Publication (Box 20, Folder 20)
      Author: Stylianos Perrakis
  - Perry, Nancy J., "Here Comes Richer, Riskier Pay Plans", Publication (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Here Come Richer, Riskier, Pay Plans, 1988; Publication (Box 20, Folder 21)
      Author: Nancy J. Perry
  - Perry, Nancy J., "Saving the Schools: How Business Can Help", Publication (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Saving the Schools: How Business Can Help, 1988; Publication (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Perry, Nancy J., "What's Powering Mexico's Success", Publication (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: What's Powering Mexico's Success, 1992; Publication (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Pesando, James E., Morley Gunderson, and Pauline Shum, "Work Incentives and Redistributive Effects of Union Pension Plans in Canada", Publication (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Work Incentives and Redistributive Effects of Union Pension Plans in Canada, 1990; Publication (Box 20, Folder 24)
      Author: James E. Pesando, Morley Gunderson, and Pauline Shum
  - Pestillo, Peter J., "Employee Involvement Enables Ford to Lead Change, not be led by it", Publication (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement Enables Ford to Lead Change, Not be Led by It, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 25)
      Author: Peter J. Pestillo
  - Peters, Tom, "Competition and Compassion", Publication (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Competition and Compassion, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 26)
      Author: Tom Peters
  - Peters, Tom and Nancy Austin, "MBWA (Management by Walking Around)", Publication (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Management by Walking Around, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 27)
      Author: Tom Peters and Nancy Austin
  - Peters, Tom, "Beyond Speed: We're All in the Fad-&-Fashion Business", Publication (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Beyond Speed: We're All in the Fad & Fashion Business, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Peters, Tom "Let's Get it Right", Publication (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Let's Get It Right, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Peters, Tom "Making it Happen", Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Making It Happen, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Peterson, Peter G., "The Morning After", Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: The Morning After, 1987; Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
      Author: Peter G. Peterson
  - Peterson, Richard B., Tracy, Lane N., "A Behavioral Model of Problem Solving in Labor Negotiations", Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: A Behavioral Model of Problem-Solving in Labour Negotiations, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
      Author: Richard B. Peterson and Lane N. Tracy
  - Peterson, Richard B., Tracy, Lane, "What Factors Encourage problem-Solving in Labor Relations", Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: What Factors Encourage Problem-Solving in Labor Relations, 1976; Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
      Author: Richard B. Peterson and Lane Tracy
  - Peterson, Steven A., Thomas A. Letko, and Wilford G. Miles, "Worker Participation and the Spillover Effect: The Case of Labor Management Committees", Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Worker Participation and the Spillover Effect: The Case of Labor-Management Committees, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
      Author: Steven A. Peterson, Thomas A. Letko, and Wilford G. Miles
  - Pfeiffer, William G., "The Road from Babel: Prospects for Integrated Office Systems", Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: The Road from Babel: Prospects for Integrated Office Systems, 1984; Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
      Author: William G. Pfeiffer
  - Philadelphia Area Labor-Management Committee, "Strategy for Progress: An Introduction to Labor Management Cooperation", Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Strategy for Progress: An Introduction to Labor Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Philippi, Jorie, "Facilitating the Flow of Information Between the Business and Education Committees", Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Facilitating the Flow of Information Between the Business and Education Committees, 1989; Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
      Author: Jorie Philippi
  - Phillips, Julien R., Management of Human Resources in the Excellent Companies, Publication (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Management of Human Resources in the Excellent Companies, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 38)
      Author: Julien R. Phillips
  - Phillips, Louis J., "Quality of Work Life: Management for the 80's", Publication (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Quality of Work Life: Management for the 80's, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 39)
      Author: Louis J. Phillips
  - Pigniol, Claude Industrial Relations and Enterprising Restructuring in France, Publication (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations and Enterprise Restructuring in France, 1989; Publication (Box 20, Folder 40)
      Author: Claude Pigniol
  - Pincus, David M., "Employee Involvement Programs as Alternative Dispute Resolution Strategies", Publication (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement Programs as Alternative Dispute Resolution Strategies, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 41)
      Author: David M. Pincus
  - pipkorn, Jorn, "The Legal Framework of Employee Participation Methods at National and International Levels and Particularly Within the European Community", Publication (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: The Legal Framework of Employee Participation Methods at National and International Levels and Particularly within the European Community, 1980; Publication (Box 20, Folder 42)
      Author: Jorn Pipkorn
  - "Plant Closed", Publication (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Plant Closed, 1980; Publication (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Platzer, Linda Cardillo, Annual Survey of Corporate Contributions, Publication (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Annual Survey of Corporate Contributions, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 44)
      Author: Linda Cardillo Platzer
  - Ploscowe, Stephen A., "Two-Tiered Compensation Plans", Publication (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Two-Tiered Compensation Plans, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 45)
      Author: Stephen A. Ploscowe
  - Plovnick, Mark S. and Gary Chaison, "Relationships Between Concession Bargaining and Labor-Management Cooperation", Publication (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Relationships Between Concession Bargaining and Labor-Management Cooperation, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 46)
      Author: Mark S. Plovnick and Gary Chaison
  - Podgursky, Michael and Paul Swaim, Labor Market Adjustment and Job Displacement: Evidence from the January 1984 Displaced Worker Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Labor Market Adjustment and Job Displacement: Evidence from the January 1984 Displaced Worker Survey, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 47)
      Author: Michael Podgursky and Paul Swaim
  - Pohl, Frances K. "Ben Shahn and Fortune Magazine: Representatives of Labor in 1946", Publication (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Ben Shahn and Fortune Magazine: Representatives of Labor in 1946, 1989; Publication (Box 20, Folder 48)
      Author: Frances K. Pohl
  - pope, Gregory. Mark, Terri Hospital Labor Markets in the 1980s, Publication (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Hospital Labor Markets in the 1980s, 1990; Publication (Box 20, Folder 49)
      Author: Gregory Pope and Terri Menke
  - Poplin, Mary "Educating in Diversity", Publication (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Educating in Diversity, 1992; Publication (Box 20, Folder 50)
      Author: Mary Poplin
  - Popson, Thomas J., "Seven Years of Experience with a Scalon Plan at TRW Airfoil Division, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania", Publication (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Seven Years of Experience with a Scanlon Plan at TRW Airfoil Division, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 51)
      Author: Thomas J. Popson
  - Popular, John J., "Labor-Management Relations by Objectives", Publication (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations by Objectives, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 52)
      Author: John J. Popular
  - Popular, John J., "Perspective: Area Labor-Management Committees", Publication (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Perspective: Area Labor-Management Committees, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Porter, Alan L., J. David Roessner, Frederick A. Rossini, and Keith R. Nelms, Final Report: Office Automations Outlook: 1985-2000, Publication (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Final Report: Office Automation Outlook: 1985-2000, Publication (Box 20, Folder 54)
      Author: Alan L. Porter, J. David Roessner, Frederick A. Rossini, and Keith R. Nelms
  - Porter, Michael E., Canada at the Crossroads; The Reality of a New Competitive Environment, Publication (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Canada at the Crossroads: The Reality of a New Competitive Envrionment, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 55)
      Author: Michael E. Porter
  - Porter, Michael E. "The Competitive Advantage of Nations", Publication (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The Competitive Advantage of Nations, Publication (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Portis, Bernard, David J. Fullerton, and Oaul R. Ingram, Quality Circles in Canada, A Review of Case Histories on Employee Involvement Programs, Publication (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles in Canada, A Review of Case Histories on Employee Involvement Programs, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 57)
      Author: Bernard Portis, David J. Fullerton, Paul R. Ingram
  - Portis, Bernard and Michael G. Suys, The Effect of Advance Notice in a Plant Shutdown, Publication (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: The Effect of Advance Notice in a Plant Shutdown, 1970; Publication (Box 20, Folder 58)
      Author: Bernard Portis and Michel G. Suys
  - Poulin, George J., "Three Survival Issues", Publication (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Three Survival Issues, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 59)
      Author: George J. Poulin
  - Power, Elizabeth. "The Way to Excellence", Publication (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: The Way to Excellence, 1990; Publication (Box 20, Folder 60)
      Author: Elizabeth Power
  - Power, Donald F., "Targeting a New Dimension to Dispute Resolution", Publication (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Targeting a New Dimension to Dispute Resolution, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 61)
      Author: Donald F. Power
  - Poza, Ernesto J., "A Do-it-Yourself Guide to Group Problem Solving", Publication (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: A Do-it-Yourself Guide to Group Problem Solving, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 62)
      Author: Ernesto J. Poza
  - Poza, Ernesto and Richard Ault, "Peopletech: A New Synthesis of People and Technology", Publication (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Peopletech: A New Synthesis of People and Technology, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 63)
      Author: Ernesto Poza and Richard Ault
  - Poza, Ernesto J. and M. Lynne Markus, "Success Story: The Team Approach to Work Restructuring", Publication (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: Success Story: The Team Approach to Work Restructuring, 1980; Publication (Box 20, Folder 64)
      Author: Ernesto J. Poza and M. Lynne Markus
  - Prasad, S. Benjamin, "The Growth of Co-Determination", Publication (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Practicing What They Teach: Total Quality Management at Oregon State University, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - "Preparing People For Work", Publication (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: The Growth of Co-Determination, 1977; Publication (Box 20, Folder 66)
      Author: S. Benjamin Prasad
  - President's Advisory Committee on Mediation and Conciliation, America Works, Publication (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Preparing People for Work Productivity Brief No.22, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - President's Commission on Competitiveness, "Human Resources and Competitiveness", Publication (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: America Works, 1988; Publication (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - President's Council on Management Improvement, Applying the Best to Government: Improving the Management of Human Resources in the Federal Government Vol. I, Publication (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Human Resources and Competitiveness, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - President's Council on Management Improvement, "U.S. Department of Labor: Integrating Human Resources and Business Planning", Publication (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Applying the Best to Government: Improving the Management of Human Resources in the Federal Government, 1987; Publication (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Prestowitz, Clyde V., Jr., "Can We Survive Technology Transfer?", Publication (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: U.S. Department of Labor: Integrating Human Resources and Business Planning, 1988; Publication (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Proctor, Barcy H., "A Sociotechnical Work-Design System at Digital Ensfield: Utilizing Untapped Resources", Publication (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: Can We Survive Technology Transfer?, 1991; Publication (Box 20, Folder 72)
      Author: Clyde V. Prestowitz Jr.
  - Productivity Programs Office, Quality Circles, Publication (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: A Sociotechnical Work-Design System at Digital Ensfield: Utilizing Untapped Resources, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 73)
      Author: Barcy H. Proctor
  - "Productivity Growth: A Better Life for America", Publication (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Productivity Panel, The Productivity Problem: U.S. Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: Productivity Growth: A Better Life for America, 1984; Publication (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - "Productivity Motivation Through Organizational Change", Publication (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: The Productivity Problem: U.S. Labor-Management Relations, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Programs for Employment and Workplace Systems, An Institute for Managers, Publication (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: Productivity Motivation Through Organizational Change, Publication (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Project 2000 Committee, Project 2000 Committee Report and Recommendations, Publication (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: An Institute for Manufacturers, 1987; Publication (Box 20, Folder 78)
      Author: Programs for Employment and Workplace Systems
  - Pruitt, Dean G., "Trends in the Scientific Study of Negotiation and Mediation", Publication (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Project 2000 Committee Report and Recommendations, 1985; Publication (Box 20, Folder 79)
      Author: Project 2000 Committee
  - Public Employee Department, Strategies to Help the Working Poor: The Union Solution, Publication (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: Trends in the Scientific Study of Negotiation and Mediation, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 80)
      Author: Dean G. Pruitt
  - Pulliam, Mark S., "Legal Aspects of Exclusive Representation: Ruminations on the Private-Public Sector Analogy", Publication (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Strategies to Help the Working Poor: The Union Solution, 1990; Publication (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Pulisipher, Allan G., "The Union Shop: A Legitimate Form of Coercion in a Free-Market Economy", Publication (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: Legal Aspects of Exclusive Representation: Ruminations on the Private-Public Sector Analogy, 1984; Publication (Box 20, Folder 82)
      Author: Mark S. Pulliam
  - "Putting the Work Ethic to Work", Publication (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: The Union Shop: A Legitimate Form of Coercion in a Free-Market Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 20, Folder 83)
      Author: Allan G. Pulsipher
  - "Quality Control Circles Pay Off Big", Publication (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: Putting the Work Ethic to Work, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - "Quality Teams: The People Who Do the Jobs Know the Jobs", Publication (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Quality Control Circles Pay Off Big, 1979; Publication (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - "Quality and Productivity The Japanese Point of View", Publication (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Quality Teams: The People Who do the Jobs Know the Jobs, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Quality of Work Life Report, "Drugs in the Workplace", Publication (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Quality and ProductivityThe Japanese Point of View, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Quality of Work Life Report, "The Renaissance of American Quality", Publication (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: Drugs in the Workplace, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - "QWL in the Bell System", Publication (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: The Renaissance of American Quality, 1986; Publication (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - "Quality Circle Boom Part of Growing American Trend", Publication (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: QWL in the Bell System, 1983; Publication (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Quality Circle: Middle Management Overview, Publication (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Quality Circle boom part of growing American trend, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - "Quality Circles", Publication (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Item 1: Quality Circle: Middle Management Overview, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - "Quality Circles", Publication (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles, 1982; Publication (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - "Quality Circles Survey Shows Significant Change in Participants' Attitudes", Publication (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - "Quality Circles Growth Increases at Honeywell", Publication (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles survey shows significant change in participants' attitudes, 1981; Publication (Box 20, Folder 95)